[{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of FED?","answerOptions":[{"answer":1610},{"answer":1502},{"answer":2662},{"answer":4077,"isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of BAE?","answerOptions":[{"answer":1308},{"answer":347},{"answer":2990,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":743}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 712?","answerOptions":[{"answer":4000},{"answer":22},{"answer":127},{"answer":1810,"isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 92D?","answerOptions":[{"answer":1999},{"answer":317},{"answer":2349,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":511}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 7D5?","answerOptions":[{"answer":3810},{"answer":3175},{"answer":2005,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":1190}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of B05?","answerOptions":[{"answer":333},{"answer":1607},{"answer":3074},{"answer":2821,"isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 40B?","answerOptions":[{"answer":282},{"answer":1390},{"answer":1725},{"answer":1035,"isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 99E?","answerOptions":[{"answer":1276},{"answer":2462,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":3844},{"answer":3904}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 7AA?","answerOptions":[{"answer":3013},{"answer":3945},{"answer":305},{"answer":1962,"isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 39F?","answerOptions":[{"answer":532},{"answer":498},{"answer":927,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":3333}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 9BA?","answerOptions":[{"answer":186},{"answer":3470},{"answer":2490,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":3150}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 59F?","answerOptions":[{"answer":553},{"answer":1974},{"answer":1439,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":2927}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 8AF?","answerOptions":[{"answer":812},{"answer":3153},{"answer":1590},{"answer":2223,"isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 1B5?","answerOptions":[{"answer":437,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":3208},{"answer":1865},{"answer":3856}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 0C2?","answerOptions":[{"answer":2106},{"answer":2441},{"answer":3298},{"answer":194,"isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 0BF?","answerOptions":[{"answer":749},{"answer":226},{"answer":1374},{"answer":191,"isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 5A3?","answerOptions":[{"answer":1664},{"answer":1443,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":1808},{"answer":511}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 9CD?","answerOptions":[{"answer":3191},{"answer":567},{"answer":2509,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":2997}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 587?","answerOptions":[{"answer":2421},{"answer":1415,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":3493},{"answer":3409}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of DC7?","answerOptions":[{"answer":3459},{"answer":3527,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":3374},{"answer":3436}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of FBC?","answerOptions":[{"answer":710},{"answer":2180},{"answer":3433},{"answer":4028,"isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 8DA?","answerOptions":[{"answer":2266,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":3176},{"answer":1424},{"answer":893}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 023?","answerOptions":[{"answer":35,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":2083},{"answer":3906},{"answer":1987}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 960?","answerOptions":[{"answer":831},{"answer":113},{"answer":2400,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":3501}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of E88?","answerOptions":[{"answer":1925},{"answer":3783},{"answer":3988},{"answer":3720,"isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 138?","answerOptions":[{"answer":312,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":1572},{"answer":250},{"answer":2848}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 52E?","answerOptions":[{"answer":1326,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":2806},{"answer":299},{"answer":3491}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 459?","answerOptions":[{"answer":3809},{"answer":2978},{"answer":1113,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":2832}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 47B?","answerOptions":[{"answer":3644},{"answer":1147,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":2995},{"answer":134}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of B95?","answerOptions":[{"answer":2965,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":1587},{"answer":3516},{"answer":398}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 60F?","answerOptions":[{"answer":134},{"answer":51},{"answer":1551,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":3764}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of F3E?","answerOptions":[{"answer":972},{"answer":4010},{"answer":3902,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":2713}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of F2B?","answerOptions":[{"answer":3089},{"answer":487},{"answer":987},{"answer":3883,"isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of EE7?","answerOptions":[{"answer":1500},{"answer":1687},{"answer":768},{"answer":3815,"isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 124?","answerOptions":[{"answer":850},{"answer":690},{"answer":315},{"answer":292,"isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 6C5?","answerOptions":[{"answer":1429},{"answer":2277},{"answer":1733,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":2196}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of F86?","answerOptions":[{"answer":1969},{"answer":540},{"answer":3974,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":1424}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 651?","answerOptions":[{"answer":1617,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":1076},{"answer":2778},{"answer":3050}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 958?","answerOptions":[{"answer":2078},{"answer":2700},{"answer":408},{"answer":2392,"isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 814?","answerOptions":[{"answer":3239},{"answer":559},{"answer":2068,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":3218}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 042?","answerOptions":[{"answer":1955},{"answer":2664},{"answer":66,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":3664}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 04E?","answerOptions":[{"answer":3894},{"answer":78,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":2293},{"answer":259}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 636?","answerOptions":[{"answer":1590,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":2640},{"answer":709},{"answer":2596}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of C31?","answerOptions":[{"answer":902},{"answer":3121,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":1739},{"answer":3751}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 780?","answerOptions":[{"answer":3987},{"answer":3489},{"answer":1920,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":3412}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of F58?","answerOptions":[{"answer":1694},{"answer":3928,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":806},{"answer":2074}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 72F?","answerOptions":[{"answer":3823},{"answer":2775},{"answer":1839,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":3085}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 1DC?","answerOptions":[{"answer":476,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":339},{"answer":792},{"answer":2349}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of B9E?","answerOptions":[{"answer":2974,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":3308},{"answer":2835},{"answer":3002}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 2DE?","answerOptions":[{"answer":1228},{"answer":3515},{"answer":734,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":2694}]}]